<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Project P1&#39;s Title on South Park Awesome Networks!</title>
    <link>https://graphs.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Project P1&#39;s Title on South Park Awesome Networks!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://graphs.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sentiment Analysis - how do our characters feel?</title>
      <link>https://graphs.github.io/apps/sentiment_analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 18:30:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graphs.github.io/apps/sentiment_analysis/</guid>
      <description>While we wanted to do a sentiment analysis, much like with the Zelda project, we unfortunately did not have any appropriate data. Wiki pages tend to be written in very neutral language, which means that while methodologies like the LabMT do work, they do produce strange results. Essentially, instead of analysing and finding the sentiment of each character, one could only find the sentiment of the character’s Wiki page itself. As will be shown by the examples below, the associated sentiment does not match with the actual character’s personality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Word Clouds: All PC down here.. (maybe?)</title>
      <link>https://graphs.github.io/apps/wordclouds/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 18:30:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graphs.github.io/apps/wordclouds/</guid>
      <description>Purpose: This is the home page to reveal the most awesome Wordclouds generated from the characters of South Park!
We have generated wordclouds for a few categories.
Note: this section is rather meant to be engaging and informal. For a more formal in-depth analysis and the source code, one can check the notebook provided in this GitHub repository - Part_B_Data_Analysis (Section: Networks and Visualization)
Wordclouds - Really good insight from just a cloud of words By analysing the SP characters and attributes, we came up to the conclusion to generate insights from generating a few wordclouds for different categories</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graphs! Series vs. the Game!</title>
      <link>https://graphs.github.io/apps/graphs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 18:30:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graphs.github.io/apps/graphs/</guid>
      <description>Purpose: This section reveals the most awesome network visualizations and network analysis for South Park!
Networks are presented based on the characters from the whole SP series and the characters only present in the &amp;lsquo;Stick of Truth&amp;rsquo; game. Let&amp;rsquo;s see what can we discover!
Note: this section is rather meant to be engaging and informal. For a more formal in-depth analysis and the source code, one can check the notebook provided in this GitHub repository - Part_B_Data_Analysis (Section: Networks and Visualization).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reveal the Stick of Truth! And DataFrame stats!</title>
      <link>https://graphs.github.io/apps/dataframe_stats/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 18:30:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://graphs.github.io/apps/dataframe_stats/</guid>
      <description>Purpose: This section will present some DataFrame visualizations. For further information regarding how this DataFrame was compiled, one can check the notebook provided in this GitHub repository - Part_A_Data_Mining (Section: DataFrame).
The Data: The information in the table above is a sneak-peak into the DataFrame object we have created using the API content of the Wiki pages of the South Park Archives (the Data Source hyperlink on the sidebar will take you to the landing page).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
